wealthcycles.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy – GoldSilver.com Customer Support

We take your privacy seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect your information. Please read this privacy policy carefully.

This Privacy Policy tells you:

  * What information we collect
  * How we use that information
  * How we may share that information
  * How we protect your information
  * Your choices regarding your personal information

This policy pertains to your use of the Goldsilver.com™ website, related translated websites (OroPlata.com™, etc.), and any other websites or applications (collectively “Sites”) operated by GoldSilver LLC (“Company”), except as otherwise stated.

By accessing the Sites, you accept the practices described below. The Company is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any website or application not operated by our Company, to which this Sites links to or which links to this Site. You are advised to be aware when you are leaving our Sites for a third party website or application.

**1\. Safeguarding your privacy.**

The security and confidentiality of your information is important to us. The Sites have incorporated certain physical, administrative and technical procedures to safeguard your personal information for all financial transactions online. Personal information may be printed or otherwise stored in a non-electronic form. Only authorized employees who have a need to access your personal information in order to perform a specific job are allowed access to your personal information.

**2\. Types of Information We Collect.**

We collect the following categories of information:

  * Registration information you provide when you create an account, including your first name and surname, country of residence, gender, date of birth, email address, username and password.
  * Transaction information you provide when you request information or purchase a product or service from us, including your postal address, telephone number and payment information.
  * Information you provide in surveys on our Sites.
  * Information you provide to us when you use our Site, or otherwise interact with our Company.
  * Usage, viewing and technical data, including your device identifier or IP address, when you visit our sites, or use our applications embedded on third-party sites.

**3\. How We Collect Your Information.**

We may collect information from you on these Sites in several different ways. We collect information you provide to us when you create an account and register on our Site, request products, services or information from us, participate in customer surveys or other activities on our Site, or otherwise interact with us. Please keep in mind that if you provide information to us from a third-party website or platform, the information you provide may be separately collected by the third-party website or platform. The information we collect is covered by this privacy policy and the information the third-party website or platform collects is subject to the third-party’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the third-party platform will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly through our applications.

We collect information through technology, such as website browser cookies, Flash cookies, advertising or user identifiers provided by the browser or application platform, and web beacons, including when you visit our Sites or use our applications on third-party sites or platforms. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a webpage, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the Sites to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases Sites navigation, and so on. When you return to the website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this or other websites that depend on cookies.

We currently use cookies to track our Sites traffic in order to enhance our information and your experience on the Site. Although cookies do not give us any personally identifiable information about you, once you choose to give us your personal information on an online form this information may be linked to cookies.

**4\. Use of Your Information by Our Company.**

We use the personal information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * To provide you with the products and services you request.
  * To communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about features on our Sites or our services or products and changes to our policies.
  * To be consistent with local law and choices and controls that may be available to you in order to:
  * Send you offers and promotions for our products and services or third-party products and services
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Site
  * To optimize or improve our products, services and operations.
  * To detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.

**5\. Sharing Your Information with Other Companies or Entities.**

We will not share your personal information outside of our Company, except in limited circumstances, including:

  * When you allow us to share your personal information with another company, such as:
  * Electing to share your personal information with carefully selected companies so that they can send you offers and promotions about their products and services.
  * Directing us to share your personal information with third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites.
  * Please note that once we share your personal information with another company, the information received by the other company becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
  * When we cooperate with financial institutions to offer co-branded products or services to you, however, we will do so only if permitted by applicable law and, in these cases, the financial institutions are prohibited from using your personal information for purposes other than those related to the co-branded products or services.
  * When companies perform services on our behalf, like package delivery, storage and customer service; however, these companies are prohibited from using your personal information for purposes other than those requested by us or required by law.
  * When we share personal information with third parties in connection with the sale of a business, to enforce our Terms of Use or rules, to ensure the safety and security of our guests and third parties, to protect our rights and property and the rights and property of our guests and third parties, to comply with legal process or governmental investigations, or in other cases if we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law.

**6\. Security of Your Information.**

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive a formal written complaint, we will contact the person and/or entity who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities and law enforcement, in order to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

**7\. Compliance and Cooperation with Regulatory Authorities.**

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we help protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Keep your password safe to help protect your accounts and personal information; it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share it. If you are sharing a computer, you should always log out before leaving our Sites or application to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**8\. Your Controls and Choices.**

We provide you with the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding our collection, use and sharing of your information. In accordance with local law, your controls and choices may include the following:

  * You may correct and update your registration account.
  * You may change your choices for Silver & Gold emails, subscriptions, newsletters and alerts. You may “opt out” of being on our mailing list or receiving future direct mailings from us by indicating your Account Preferences.

You may exercise your controls and choices, or request access to your personal information, by logging into your Silver & Gold online account, and selecting “Preferences”, or by emailing Silver & Gold Inc. at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#70191e161f30171f1c1403191c0615025e131f1d) and following instructions provided in communications sent to you.

Please be aware that, if you do not allow us to collect personal information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain products and services to you, and some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If you have questions regarding the specific personal information about you that we process or retain, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2b42454d446b4c44474f5842475d4e5905484446).

**9\. Data Security, Integrity and Retention.**

We may transfer your personal information to individual and subsidiary companies of Silver & Gold, Inc. or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this privacy policy. Wherever your personal information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of your personal information.

**10\. Data Transfers, Storage and Processing.**

The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We will retain your personal information for the length of time needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy.**

From time to time, we may change this privacy policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy policy. We will provide notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent when necessary. Notice may be by email to you at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on our Sites, or by other means, consistent with applicable law. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. In addition, we may freely assign this Privacy Policy or any of our rights and/or obligations hereunder.

**12\. Comments and Questions**

If you have a comment or question about this privacy policy, please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f990979f96b99e96959d8a90958f9c8bd79a9694). Our Sites may contain links to other sites not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our sites or applications and to read the privacy policies of other sites that may collect your personal information.

_Notice to California Residents:_  If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Silver & Gold, Inc. to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this privacy policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write us at:

Attn: CA Privacy Rights  
GoldSilver LLC  
PO Box 8099  
Calabasas, CA 91372

Last Updated: June 30, 2016 21:39
